https://www.welcomm.co.uk/customer-hub/terms-conditions

Terms and Conditions
Call and Email Monitoring:
Please note that telephone calls and email correspondence may be recorded for quality control and training purposes.
Website Conditions of Use:
Your use of the website (www.welcomm.co.uk) is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with the following terms and conditions of use:
Copyright – This Site is produced, owned and maintained by Welcomm Communications Ltd. All information appearing on the Site (‘the Content’) is the property of Welcomm Communications Ltd or its suppliers and is protected by international copyright laws. None of the Content other than that which is specifically offered for download by Welcomm Communications Ltd may be downloaded, copied, reproduced, republished, posted, transmitted, stored, sold or distributed without the prior written permission of the copyright holder.
Welcomm Communications Ltd. reserves the right to modify their terms and conditions of use at any time without prior notice. Any changes will be noted on this page and it is the responsibility of the user to ensure they are aware of any such changes.
Disclaimer – Welcomm Communications Ltd. has made every reasonable effort to ensure that the information contained within the website is up to date and accurate. It is provided on the understanding that Welcomm Communications Ltd. shall not be liable under any circumstances for any consequential loss or damages (including, without limitation, loss of contract, loss of use, loss of profit or other economic loss and whether caused by the negligence of ourselves, our employees or agents or otherwise) which arises out of or in connection with the information provided on the Site.
For all Terms and Conditions, please review the attached documents below.
Welcomm Covid-19 Health and Safety Risk Assessment
General terms and conditions for supply of deliverables
Schedule a – specific terms mobile phone supply
Schedule b – specific terms it support and services supply
Schedule c – specific terms unified products and services supply
Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions
0800 064 64 64  |  CustomerCare@welcomm.co.uk
Copyright © 2020 Welcomm Communications Ltd - all rights reserved
About Us
Communications
Technology
Smart Safety
Utilities
Case Studies
Blogs
Contact Us
Revoke Cookie consent
Mitel MiVoice Office 250 Brochure
Please tick the box to confirm your consent to us using your personal information to contact you in relation to this enquiry.
For more information read our Privacy Policy
I Consent
CLOSE
Test PopUp
Please tick the box to confirm your consent to us using your personal information to contact you in relation to this enquiry.
For more information read our Privacy Policy
I Consent
CLOSE
Please tick the box to confirm your consent to us using your personal information to contact you in relation to this enquiry.
For more information read our Privacy Policy
I Consent
×
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. The cookies allow us to administer our website, analyse our traffic and provide useful features to you. To manage your cookie settings click manage your cookie preferences or visit our Privacy Policy page.I ACCEPTI DO NOT ACCEPTPRIVACY POLICY
You can revoke your consent any time using the revoke consent button.Revoke Cookie consent
